sellanycar.com 2017-06-06

# SellAnyCar.com | Sell Any Car to us! Guaranteed purchase. Find out your car's value for FREE now

## Privacy Policy

When you use our website SellAnyCar.com, we ask you for some personal contact information. We might record any video, audio, digital communication or interaction you might have with us. We may use your information to send you marketing material such as our newsletter, which you may unsubscribe at any point. 

Your personal information will be held and used, but will not be disclosed to any unauthorized person or body. Where appropriate, we may use such information in carrying out marketing activity, research activity or any activity as we deem fit. 

We may share information with carefully selected vendors and business partners with whom we work. This includes companies that offer affinity, frequent-user, and reward programs; and, companies that perform marketing services and other business operations not limited in its nature. We may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns and related site information to reputable third party vendors. We may disclose Personal Information we collect from you if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that disclosure is necessary (a) to obey the law or comply with legal process served on us or our affiliates; (b) to protect and defend our rights or property or the rights or property of other users of our Site; or (c) to act in an emergency to protect the personal safety of users of our Site or the public. We may disclose your detailed vehicle information to registered business partners, traders, wholesalers, the general public, or any other entity or platform, including offline and online, we see fit to globally and publicly advertise and facilitate a purchase or sale or any other commercial activity. 

Sometimes we may drop cookies on your computer after visiting our website to deliver personalized adverts while you browse the internet. 

**What are cookies?**

Like the majority of sites on the internet our site uses cookies. We collect internet log information and details of visitor behavior patterns through the use of these cookies when you visit https://www.SellAnyCar.com. We collect this information anonymously so you cannot be identified and to get the most from our site you will need to have cookies enabled. 

We do also have relationships with monitored third party suppliers that may also set cookies during your visit to be used for remarketing purposes. 

**What is a cookie exactly?**

A HTTP cookie is a small piece of data that can be stored by your computer's hard drive. It allows the site you are visiting to work more efficiently by providing information to the owner of the site. Based on this anonymous information we are then able to note the areas that may need improving and thereby improve your satisfaction with our website. 

Cookies do not contain confidential or personal information about you, such as your address, telephone number or credit card details. 

Cookies also utilize details of your valuation in order to serve relevant targeted advertisements from selected third party remarketing suppliers when visiting other websites. 

**Managing Cookies**

By using our site you accept that we will drop cookies on your machine. 

Cookies are fairly easy to manage, if cookies aren't enabled on your computer, it will mean that your experience on our website will be limited and you may not be able to use certain sections as they were intended to be used, such as the valuation engine. 

**Consent To Processing Globally.**

By providing any Personal Information to SellAnyCar.com, all users, including, without limitation, users in the Middle East countries and Globally, fully understand and unambiguously consent to this Privacy Policy and to the transfer of such Personal Information across international borders in accordance with SellAnyCar.com standard operations, including the collection, storage, and processing of such information globally. 

SellAnyCar.com FZE is located at Sharjah Airport International Free Zone, Executive Lounge, Main building, PO 120123, Sharjah UAE. Our email address is info@sellanycar.com. You can reach us under telephone number . 

If you would like to unsubscribe from our emails, please follow the link that is displayed at the bottom of any email that you have received from us. 

**CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

The Web is an evolving medium. If we decide to change this Privacy Statement at some point in the future, we'll post the changes here and update the reference to the effective date to reflect the date of the amendment. By using our Service on or after the effective date of any such amendment, you agree that your use, and any dispute over privacy, is governed by this Privacy Statement, as amended.

This privacy policy was last updated on 23.03.2017
